Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
We're ready to get out
there and get fishing.
It's been one of my dreams
and goals to make it up here.
I've been to Alaska a few
times. but never to fish.
Just our vacations
and to hang out with family.
And everything up here that
I've experienced so far is just
so much bigger.
Everything's scaled up.
Smells different.
feels different.
There's a lot of risk
that comes into it.
But...
I just want my kids to know that
I want them to work
towards your dreams and goals.
Don't let anything
slow you down.
Yeah. it's gonna be fun.
I'm just fortunate
that I fell in love with it.
Right now...
we're in the most remote
place on Earth.
smack-dab in the middle
of the Bering Sea.
This is St. George Island.
part of the Pribilof Islands.
which is about 200 miles north
of the Aleutian Chain.
And in the '60s and '70s.
this was the northernmost
jumping-off point
for fishing
in the Bering Sea.
I mean. for years.
we hunted different types
of crab up north.
That included pureblood
northern king crab.
These crab were
genetic monsters.
You know. they had
a thicker shell.
They were bigger.
They were brighter in color.
They were beautiful.
But we haven't seen them
in 30 years.
And according to this survey...
I think they're back.
When you're talking about
fishing in the north...
there is no forgiveness.
Whoa!
Run. run. run. run!
We're talking shallower
waters. bigger waves...
heavy tides...
sub-zero temperatures.
But we gotta seek
before we find.
-Whoo!
-Here it comes!
-Here's a big one.
-Look out!
Hey!
Chart a new strategy.
Whoo!
Keep faith in our captains.
Trust our experience.
- Fire. fire!
-Got an exhaust leak.
Oh. no!
Fight through the pain.
-What happened?
-You all right? Looks terrible.
These northern crab...
-Going over.
-Yeah!
...it means $60 million
for the fleet.
-Boom!
-Let's go!
-Big pots!
-Yeah!
-What?
Yeah!
Oh. whoa. whoa. whoa.
-Blah!
Get down!
We have to embrace a power
greater than ourselves.
Vessel calling Mayday.
Oh. my God.
Careful.
Let's go. let's go.
Watch out!
And rise to fish again.
October.
Dutch Harbor. Alaska.
Got a little present.
Christmas come early. baby.
We're going way far up north.
Gonna be really cold.
keep your hands warm.
-Right on. right on.
Stay safe. stay warm.
They had these penis warmers.
but I didn't grab them.
Pots are coming on
the boat. baby!
Here we go.
Yeah!
Felt that inch go in there.
That's what we want.
For the first time
in 27 years...
Overhead.
OK. good.
Let's go fishing!
Big money. baby!
Big money trip.
...the Bering Sea crab fleet
prepares for a fall season in
upper latitudes north
of St. George Island.
Feels good swinging some pots.
Yeah. baby!
Every year they do a survey.
and. um. they found a trace
of crab up north.
twice as big as the crab we fish
in the middle of Bristol Bay.
Their own breed. big crab.
so. shh. that's where
I'm going fishing.
Spurred by the Alaska
Department of Fish and Game's
annual survey...
- Here we go.
-Yes. sir.
...captains bet on
the reemergence
of an ancient. larger crab.
descending from the Arctic
into fishable grounds --
the pureblood red king.
These crabs have been sitting
up here all alone because
they haven't been fished
in 20 years.
They're denser meat.
and they're big.
With the smallest legal red
king crab carapace spanning
six and a half inches.
northern red kings
can tout a 50% larger shell
and fetch a premium price
of $30 per meaty pound.
If we go up there and we hit
the mother lode. the price of
our crab is gonna go
from here to here.
-How's that. good?
-Yep.
But those seas
are treacherous.
To seize their share
of the fleet-wide.
2.4 million pound.
$72 million fall season
payday. captains must scour
the 55.000-square-mile northern
territory. where the shallower
sea floor creates shredding
currents and towering waves.
It's gonna be a gamble.
But if I nail them.
bang!
It'll be in. out. unce.
unce. unce. pow!
220 miles north
of Dutch Harbor.
How you doing. man?
Good. good. good. good. good.
- You ready to go?
- Yeah.
Hey. I thought you were
a little taller.
-Can you reach that door?
I need a booster seat.
OK.
So did they write this when
they knew you were gonna come
in the truck or what?
This "no smoking" sign.
That wasn't there before
you landed on the island.
- So where are we going?
ROVs down there.
It's all set up.
Should be ready to go.
Two days before the start of
the season. Captain Sig Hansen
and retired skipper turned boat
owner Wild Bill Wichrowski
undertake a scouting mission
using a high-tech underwater
remote-operated vehicle
to locate the premium
northern red king.
These crab.
I know they're out there.
It's just we gotta find them.
I mean. if you can get
the camera down to the bottom.
get a good visual.
you might find some
of those purebreds
that are out there.
The ROV guy. he's inside.
Don't touch anything.
He's real picky.
I'll keep my hands
off the equipment.
Sig. this is Tom.
So what do we got?
This is a seven-thruster ROV.
It has a high-definition camera
on it.
-It has a multi-beam sonar.
-How deep can this thing go?
4.000 feet.
I worry about how fast we can
go and to cover the bottom.
That's my big concern.
What's our timeline?
It's gonna be tight.
We know we wanna fish north.
That's as far
as we've gotten so far.
OK.
Well. I've been from
there to the north-northwest.
I mean. going off the survey
here. that's the spot
right there.
So the hope is
that's just the tip
of that iceberg.
and it just gets
better up above.
But I haven't been
that far up and over
in that direction ever. so.
That's an awful lot
of square miles.
Well. you better get busy.
Did I mention my daily rate
for putting all this together?
Well. I thought this was based
on friendship.
Well. that means the rate
goes up.
Clark's here.
-He's right tying up right now.
- OK.
I'll get the guys up here.
and then they'll help you
with all this stuff.
and we'll get it on board.
All right.
What's your wife's name?
Jenna Anderson.
So how long you guys
been married?
- 13 years.
- OK.
-Kids?
- Three kids.
And have you guys
already physically separated?
-Are you still living --?
- For eight months.
OK.
What are the key assets
that you've acquired
during your marriage?
-Um...
-A house.
- OK.
-That we're selling.
-OK.
What about business interest?
-Uh. we have interest in a boat.
- OK.
Titan Explorer.
So Jake.
I don't want you investing any
more money in your ownership
interest on the Titan Explorer.
because that can end up being
an asset that needs to be
divided in the case.
Well. after 17 years being
together. 13 years married.
Jen and I have decided
to call it quits.
It's due to a lot of things.
The major one is that...
I'm gone too much --
crab fishing.
But I got three little ones
that need to eat.
that have to go to school.
that have to have
doctor's appointments.
And I don't have a job.
I gotta figure out something.
Back in Dutch Harbor.
- OK. here we go.
-Pull!
-There you go.
-Whoa!
That right there is good. boys!
-Do it. boy!
-OK. good!
It's so beautiful
this time of year.
Isn't it pretty?
On the Time Bandit.
Our quota's up
from last year about 30%.
We got about 60.000.
65.000 pounds to catch.
Over a million bucks worth
of crabbies.
So I have to be quick and fast.
My dad was legendary up north.
He had a secret spot.
That guy could fish. man.
He was a fishing son
of a bitch.
I miss him.
Love you. Pops.
Love you. Dad.
Different time.
different bandits.
Different time bandits.
But I got a great team.
Steve Roberts. Teddy Bear.
Neil. the real Neil Hillstrand.
Heather Hillstrand.
-Yes!
Freddy. the Hurricane. Maugatai.
Wah!
Ah!
30 years
Freddy's been out here.
One of the best crew members
you ever met.
Strong. loyal. good
at everything. the best
on deck for decades.
So I think I got one
of the best crews
I've had in a long time.
Hey. big boss man Keith.
Um. I know the season
start really soon here.
I'm taking a job
OK.
So you're working with
the Time Bandits now?
.
Freddy's not coming with us.
I had Freddy penciled in.
You know. give me
a  call. John.
Just give me a courtesy call.
Speak of the devil.
Looks like he's heading in
right now.
Looks like he's coming to get
his gear right here.
-Is Joe around?
I got an issue right now
with Johnathan on Time Bandit.
John's got some gear over there
on the dock.
We're gonna make loading
that gear miserable.
We're gonna weld
his pots together.
What do you think?
Johnathan sent me
a message with his silence.
I'm gonna send Johnathan
a message
with something
that's very obvious.
Unce. unce. unce.
Welcome to
Dutch Harbor. Johnathan.
I got these 20 pots.
As soon as we grab those.
we're going north.
Let's get some more bullets
for the hunt.
We're getting our pots
loaded. getting ready
for the season here.
We'll be ready for killing
some crab here soon.
We're good.
Up.
Roger!
-Heads up!
-Whoa. whoa. whoa!
-Whoa!
-!
Hey. watch out!
Watch out!
OK. good!
!
Hey. watch out!
Watch out!
Whoa. whoa. whoa!
What happened?
You OK?
-Is everyone OK?
-!
What ?
That whole  stack just
went over sideways.
The pots.
they're welded together.
No .
-Are you kidding me?
-Last one was.
-It's so big.
- So it's welded?
Yes. sir.
Somebody welded
our pots together.
It's all tac welded.
Well. Heather should
never left it here. but...
Did I tell you I bought
you a truck. Teddy Bear?
This is yours.
I bought you this
for your birthday.
So go put it in
storage somewhere.
.
Hey. Freddy's over there.
You got a Wizard deckhand.
.
That's how...
Keith always forgets Roadrunner
always beats Coyote.
Roadrunner's too fast.
too smart.
Beep. beep. .
Time's ticking.
-All clear!
-Good. go ahead.
Every hour that passes brings
us one more hour closer
to the start of king crab.
Ready to fill this boat up.
Bring 'em on board.
Yes. sir.
Hey. what's going on?
I'm sorry to hear
about you and Jenna.
That was a big surprise.
I'm sorry. too.
...there is someone
that might be looking for
He said he had something
you might be interested in.
Here's the Spit Dock right here.
Slip 42 at the end.
There's 36 right there.
37.
Let's see.
Let's see what he's got.
Wow.
Cornelia Marie.
In the pantheon of Bering Sea
greats. no ship is better known
than the Cornelia Marie.
For years this boat was
Phil Harris'.
And no legend looms larger
than Captain Phil Harris.
Everybody wants the big time.
they just don't
wanna work for it.
Whoo!
Famed for hunting down 40
million career pounds of crab.
Phil pushed his beloved
Cornelia Marie...
I always had a dream
that I'd die out here.
...and himself to the limit.
It's gonna be a heavy
tobacco consumption day today.
Until a mid-season stroke cut
his life short
at the age of 53.
It's all I've ever done.
It's my whole life.
It's a good boat.
I've worked on it before.
I was young.
I had just met Jenna.
I was getting yelled
at all the time.
Life was hard for me.
Did you hurt
your girlish figure?
I mean. there was a lot of
things that were going on back
then that I don't really
wanna go back to.
But one thing that was good was
that I got to fish with Phil.
Got all our tender equipment
on. you can see.
So she's been
working for salmon.
Take a look down below.
This is definitely shut down.
Watch your feet here. Sam.
Whoa!
Looks like the generator's
under construction.
There's the parts.
Let's get upstairs.
Let's see what we got.
Phew. dusty!
Feels pretty good.
Feels real good.
But the generator being down.
I don't know if I have
enough time
before the season starts
to undertake a project
like this.
The reason why Phil was
so loved. admired.
and respected was because
he had his own demons.
But it didn't stop Phil
from thriving in this business.
I'm gonna have to keep trying.
I don't know if his spirit's
still in the boat.
but if it is. we'll catch crab.
Like he did.
Hey. Roger.
This is Jake.
Eighty miles above
St. George Island...
-Got it?
-Go over.
Yeah. buddy!
...on the Northwestern.
Going down.
OK. here we go.
Just hours before the start of
the season. Captain Sig Hansen
pioneers a first-ever
underwater survey to locate
the elusive. rarefied reds.
60 feet now.
90 feet.
Got 200.
Are you on the bottom?
-He should hit the bottom now.
-OK. here we go.
We're on the bottom.
Well. let's start looking.
Sig's plan?
Divide a small 100 square-mile
piece of the grounds north of
St. George into sections using
the ROV's thousand feet of line
to scan one-quarter mile
at a time for any
sign of the northern kings.
So that's mud.
That's what we're looking
for there.
Is that an anemone?
I don't know what that is.
Come on.
-What's it--
- What's that?
-That's a bairdi right there.
- Oh!
- Nice.
-Bairdi?
-That's life. He's alive.
- Oh!
That's life.
This is the bottom end.
But we'll keep going
north or northwest.
OK.
And then just keep
dropping. you know?
Uh. let's bring it up.
Yeah.
Let's get it up.
OK.
Start pulling them in.
Roger.
I think. you know. what Bill
and I talked about should work.
but the crab have to be there.
North of St. George Island.
Hey. what's up?
...sense.
What do we got?
Hmm.
Hm. hm. hm.
On your plotter. can you pull
up previous fishing years
and look at where you set gear?
2013. maybe 2017?
What I'm seeing is...
where I was there
and then where I ended.
It's consistently tracking...
Yeah. let me get to it.
New plan.
So we are heading northeast.
Colder temperatures.
You gotta hold
four knots. right?
-That's your max speed?
- It is.
Well. that's
what we're gonna do.
-So there's one last shot.
-All right.
Colder water. northeast.
four knots. that's it.
All right.
Hey. let's get that thing
in the water.
-Roger.
- Keep it in gear. Karl.
All right. I got it.
All right. Imma go.
Going down.
-Is that a cod?
- Yeah.
Codfish.
I mean. it's life. right?
We just keep going.
Just kick it in gear
a little faster.
There's a lot of fish
right there.
Come on.
What are those?
- Oh!
-Oh.
-He's moving.
-Look at him walk.
Stay on him.
OK.
All right.
That's crazy.
In the tank.
they crawl sideways.
They kinda go --
Lead me to your leader.
Oh!
- Oh.
Dude. slow down a little bit.
It's one. two. three.
I counted six. seven. eight.
Those are the two
you went over?
That's about a dozen crab
right there.
There's some more
in the background.
Look at this.
They look huge.
That's male. male. male. male.
See it?
Those are the northern crab
right there.
See that?
Big. big. big. big. big.
They're climbing all on top
of each other.
Well. you're marking
all this up. right?
- I am.
- We got a good
starting point.
We gotta get Tom
off the boat.
We got 'em.
Up.
There you go.
Good.
Let's go fishing. baby.
King crab 2025.
Fish on. baby.
I'm ready to catch
some  king crab.
So I'm going to fish
king crab. Cade.
Yeah. I'm gonna get
you something when I get back.
What do you want?
Tell him you're going to fish
king crab and he --
he knows it means money.
Hey. coming in.
Have any of you guys
seen Anderson?
-We gotta get rolling.
-Yeah. roger.
It would just be nice if
he could get his ass down
to the boat so I can get
off the dock.
because we got just over
115.000 pounds of king crab.
That's $2.9 million.
which we haven't had that
in the past three years.
So. I mean. this could be
a huge season for us.
Roger's crew from
the Cornelia Marie is working
on the generator right now.
Rick Shelford's got a spot on
his boat for a deckhand.
so I'm going king crab fishing
and there's a lot of money
to be made.
If I can fish a trip with him
until the Cornelia Marie
gets fixed.
if they get the boat
ready in time.
Oh.
OK. here we go.
Let's fill the boat.
-We're good.
-OK.
You're good.
Based on the survey. based on
the water temperatures.
we're gonna be going
further north.
Working in the compass rose for
the first time in over a decade.
And nobody has that canyon
plotted out like I do.
OK. good!
It's supposed to be
around here.
Is that it?
Gotta be.
Right there.
Give me a minute. would you?
You know. there's been a lot
of boats go down
over the years. but. uh...
the Destination was one that
Sig's best friend
was the captain.
The memorial is a bench facing
the direction of where the boat
was found. and all the names
are etched in it.
It came over the radio and...
Last known position was right
on the northwest tip
of St. George.
You saw Sig's face
and his expression. that was...
It was horrific.
They found a life ring.
They found a fuel slick.
They found debris.
No life rafts. no survival
suits. no nothing.
It's just a reminder that...
the further north you go.
the more dangerous it gets.
I haven't been on deck
in 11 years.
Welcome aboard. man.
-How you doing?
-Ah.
I could be doing a lot better.
Well. just in case you kind of
feel a little bit lonely.
I got an extra bunk
in my stateroom.
That way. if you need to talk
or cuddle or anything.
I'll be right there.
I'll take you up on that
right now. man.
-Hell no. man.
-Damn. you know. man.
Lord. please protect us
while we're at sea.
The lesson is
our God always. now and ever.
And unto ages and ages.
Amen.
We will need you
to guide us.
Oh. heavenly King.
the comforter.
the spirit of truth.
who art everywhere.
present and fill this all needs.
Hey. guys. the priest
is coming.
You wanna meet me up here
on the bow?
-Yeah. Roger.
-Roger.
Let us pray to the Lord.
Lord. have mercy.
Give us the wisdom
to watch out for each other.
- Is our guy here?
- Yeah.
-Bring him on board.
-Yeah!
Come on. bring it in!
Bring it in!
I need a guy.
Freddy said.
"I got the perfect guy."
OJ Bauer!
Yeah!
I hate to tell
Keith this. but I happened
to hire his deck boss.
Protect us
from the North. Lord.
Protect us from the wind.
the weather.
Holy God.
holy mighty. holy immortal.
have mercy on us.
Holy God. holy mighty.
holy immortal.
have mercy on us.
We're going further
north than we've been.
You're gambling more expenses.
and you will see some
of the most horrendous waves
you've ever seen in your life.
I mean. it's a treasure hunt.
I'm a treasure hunter.
We'll be out on the bow
in a second.
The priest is here.
Lord. watch over us.
This vessel is blessed
by the Holy Spirit.
This vessel is blessed.
And return us to safe harbor.
In the name of the Father.
-And the Son.
-Son.
Son.
-And the Holy Spirit.
Holy Spirit.
In Jesus' name.
Amen.
And Jeff.
keep an eye out for us.
would ya?
All right. guys.
let's get to work.
-Whoo-hoo.
king crab 2025. baby.
- Hell. yeah.
-Here we go.
-Whoo!
Time to go fishing.
All right.
Whoo!
Ready going from being a captain
to deckhand real quick.
Cut her loose.
2025 king crab. Freddy.
Yeah!
-Yeah!
- Yeah. baby!
Whoo!
We gotta get the
out of here.
Roger. start the thruster.
Let's go. let's go. let's go!
Let's go to war.
All right. bud. give me
a report when you get out there.
Will do.
OK. you guys are ready?
-We can toss them whenever.
-Roger.
-Roger!
Let's go!
Well. here we go.
Well. hopefully we find
those northern red crab.
We know where they are.
We found them.
But they do move.
The more north you go.
the more dangerous it is so.
hopefully these guys are
careful and they get
the job done.
Going king crabbing
2025. yeah!
Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
Seventy five miles
north of Dutch Harbor.
We're gonna be further
north than anybody in the fleet
fished in 20 years.
Captains and their crews...
...steam 28 hours above
St. George Island...
25 years I've waited
to put pots here.
These pureblood king crab.
we might find
a frickin' mother lode.
...into the violent northern
Bering Sea.
We're way. way up north
above and beyond
where any normal
person would go.
Freddy!
Look at this.
Oh!
Anybody need a hose?
Get some. baby!
Welcome home. OJ!
-Whoo!
-Welcome to the Time Bandit!
- Welcome home.
- Whoo!
-Mu-wah!
Mah!
Whoo-hoo!
-Now you're a Time Bandit. baby.
-Yes!
That's gross.
First pot of
the season. baby.
This is the day we've been
looking for all year long.
First pot of the season!
We're out in this deep gut
in 29 fathoms.
And we're gonna just set
a 82-pound string
right down the gut.
-Going over. man.
Yep.
Going over. Teddy.
Come back loaded.
-Come back loaded.
-Whoo!
I have a Hansen sighting
on my radar.
30 miles northwest.
Hey. Sig. you got me here?
John.
Right now. I'm working
with Bill.
So I can't just be going around
sharing that information.
Loose lips sink ships. man.
He was my buddy a year ago.
We were best friends.
and now they got radio silent.
We're getting ghosted.
Oh. yeah!
Let's go!
-King crab!
We gotta go a little
by our gut and a little bit of
what the new technology says.
20 miles southeast.
Good to be alive for
red crab 2025.
Aboard the Wizard.
The survey is
showing the crab further north.
Everything is pointing
to further north.
So we are at the canyon
that's on the east side
of the compass rose.
and this doesn't look like
a canyon. all right?
But it is.
And hopefully.
we find something.
50 miles southwest.
For this area.
southeast of George.
my grandpa had epic king crab
fishing right around here.
On the Aleutian Lady.
Jake appears to be doing well.
I mean. going
through a divorce...
...you're gonna be down.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah. baby. yeah!
What the !
King crab 2025!
Yeah!
What the
do you even say?
-Jake Anderson.
Going over.
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Hang on!
.
-Whoa!
Douched!
We just got douched!
The weather's a little
bit different up north here.
It's shallower. it's windier.
which means bigger tides.
bigger waves.
It's just worse weather.
Watch out!
I better take over here now.
Oh. man.
Just watch out. guys.
It's our last string.
We almost got them all in.
We got some 35.
40 footers here.
So it's gonna slow down.
The problem is. if the sea's
getting any bigger and I have
a wave come over that
wave wall there. it's gonna
wash somebody overboard.
So I've gotta really
be careful.
. .
See how we don't
.
Watch out. guys!
Watch out. watch out!
Watch out. man!
Just be careful. everyone.
We've got such shallow
water here.
Shallower water makes
the waves even bigger.
Look out!
Gee. wow. wow.
That was a big one.
They're getting bigger quick.
This is  scary.
We got a big one coming
on the starboard.
-Run. run. run. big one coming.
-Come on. come on.
There's a big one
coming. watch out!
Go. go. go!
Guys run. run. run.
Big one coming.
- Come on. come on.
There's a big one.
watch out. watch out!
Go. go. go!
Whew.
God just blessed us
right there. dude.
You see that ?
Right on. Stephen.
-Whoo!
Good job.
Thank you. captain!
Sorry about that.
I should have
warned you earlier.
All right!
Whoo!
Yes!
Roger!
Three más.
That could have been fatal.
Fatal -- fatal blows
for the Time Bandit.
Thank you. God.
All right.
Everything is coming down
to this point.
This is where we inspected
this area with the ROV.
Far north. we did see
crab on the bottom.
and we're hoping
that they're still here.
Nothing is a guarantee.
Crab.
On three.
-One. two. three.
- Crab!
All right. guys.
Let's go do it.
-Stay safe.
-Yeah.
We've got a bunch
of ground to ourselves.
We're really far
to the northeast
into the compass rose.
Let's hope we've found
the best part of it.
This is our canyon.
My dad used to fish in this gut
up here by Cape Newenham Gut.
We're up here pulling
our first pot.
Come on. Lady Luck.
Come on. God.
I don't believe in Lady Luck.
I shouldn't have said that.
I'm not gonna say nothing.
I'm knocking on wood.
OK. moment of truth.
First pot. king crab.
Here we go.
All righty.
Let's find this first spot.
Get busy.
We need some crab.
Come on!
-Come on. crabs.
-What the hell?
-Oh. no!
- Oh. great.
Get your  totes out.
We found the females
and the babies.
This is not what
we were looking for.
Coming up.
Come on. first pot.
Damn it.
Looking pretty weak.
There's some crab!
Whoo!
-Let's  go!
-Real crab.
-They're big?
-That'll work!
-Now that's a table.
-Yeah. yeah.
They're big?
They're big!
-We have money!
-Yeah!
Yeah!
That's what I'm talking about
right there.
They're all the same.
-That's what we want.
Whoo!
Those are monsters.
Oh. he's beautiful.
-He's beautiful.
-Yeah!
Look how pretty
he is on the back.
Oh yeah.
-Nice and white.
-White.
- Look at that.
-Looks solid.
Solid.
Northern reds. boys.
Get 'em in the tank.
Come on. baby.
Very disturbing here.
Very disturbing.
I'll figure out
what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna set
these somewhere.
There's the Northwestern.
I'll try to call him up again.
Hey. Hansen. you on here?
Hansen. Hansen. Hansen.
Probably not gonna even
answer me anymore.
Hey. John.
Coyote.
Roadrunner.
I haven't heard one peep
from Hansen.
Oh. really?
You know. we got him
right here.
Interesting.
He is definitely...
Oh. wow.
Look at that  there.
They're jumping towards
the northeast
like they're tracking something.
Don't trust...
There's some crab.
but not a lot out.
OK. pull out.
You can set. and I can set
in front of him. and we'll slow
that area up.
If I can -- if I can
delay Sig...
Count me in.
All right.
All right. buddy.
...when Sig gets on crab.
it's amazing how his 27 radios.
his three telephones.
all seem to evaporate.
That's Sig Hansen.
Out here. the unspoken rule
is this --
you don't betray your partner.
and you do not
hold out on information.
I don't know. however
many throws it's gonna take
you to get me close
enough to get it.
You want me to go five.
six knots or seven knots?
Or do you want me to.
like. back her down and stop
right on the side of the boat?
Wherever you put 'em.
I'll get them for ya.
I don't think you'll be able
to get 'em by me.
-Whoo!
-Ah!
-Yeah!
-Yeah. Rick. that was good!
Yeah. roger.
Let's go. baby!
-All right!
- Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Get it. get it. get it.
dawg. get it. get it. get it.
That was actually pretty
damn good.
Here we go!
First pot. baby!
-Yeah. whoo!
-Come on. come on. come on!
First one coming up.
Red king crab 2025.
Farthest north string.
Let's hope my grandpa's spot
pays off.
Coming up.
I think this could be money.
What do we got?
Come on. come on.
come on!
-Show us some crab.
-I think this could be money.
-Coming up.
-What do we got?
-Yeah!
Yeah!
Yeah. right!
-Smells good!
-Yeah. baby.
Let's go.
Fifty-two.
That's what we're looking for.
Oh. yeah. baby.
Whoo-hoo-hoo. baby!
-Oh. yeah.
-Oh. yeah. baby.
Money in the bank. baby!
- Damn!
Hell. yeah. 64!
-This is --
-Pretty hot fishing. man!
-That was good!
- Hell. yeah. man!
We landed on 'em!
I don't care what your crew
says about you.
This has been soaking
for a day.
One day.
And we're making about
$150.000 an hour.
I mean. my grandpa's area
is amazing.
Yeah!
-Hey. Jake.
- Yep?
Roger.
Good.
How's the Cornelia Marine?
Do you think we can get the CM
up and running for king crab?
All right. bye-bye.
Come on. baby.
Riders!
It's a pretty big deal.
I just don't know
if it's gonna be
ready by the end of king crab.
-Yeah baby!
-Yeah!
-Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
I'm following
the best fishing.
and that best fishing is moving
up to the north.
So we're gonna get our gear
resituated and hope and pray
I'm making the right choice.
70 miles northeast...
on the Northwestern.
There's some crab!
Whoo!
How many in that one?
Nice!
I think the ROV plan is coming
to fruition.
I had my doubts. but. uh...
Here it comes.
...you know. the numbers
don't lie.
Womp. womp. womp.
Oh. dang.
Really?
Roger.
...to the northeast.
We might be tracking north now.
Oh. here it is.
Not too sexy.
Well. we can adjust.
You know. when we get these set
back out. we're gonna just
start setting them due north.
Yeah. dude.
If we kept going east.
we'd be in a desert.
So they're fast.
They're moving.
Good news is. right now.
we're out here all alone.
We've got it for ourselves.
We just gotta keep dialing in.
We should be able
to figure this out.
-You seeing that?
-Coming in hot.
What?
- Roger!
Sig don't answer my calls.
Lord. they know not
what they do.
They know not what they do.
What?
Company.
damn it.
Gonna give Keith
enough time to cram a bunch
of gear in that spot
Sig's gonna go to.
Gives the Coyote enough time to
just come in and do some damage.
Yeah. baby.
God bless America.
And pirates. too.
Whoo.
It's Johnathan.
You on this one. John?
You on here?
Time Bandit.
-Johnathan.
- Now Sig
wants to talk to us.
-Whoa. !
-Whoa.
-Uh-oh.
Oh. no.
What's he doing?
We're going pirate mode. baby.
First. I'm gonna blind him.
Then. I'm gonna go right
down on a string and grab
as many pots as I can.
Let's go.
Chop. chop. chop. chop.
Get in there.
Don't be shy.
We're coming for ya.
-You guys ready?
- Yeah.
Let's go. baby!
-Light 'em up.
Yeah!
Time Bandits forever!
Dude.
What the hell?
Yeah!
That's a lot of smoke.
It's a smoke screen.
Do we pillage?
Do we plunder?
- What the?
Time Bandits forever!
I can't see .
I don't see him anymore.
I don't know what the hell
he's doing.
John!
Would you answer me.
damn it?
That's pirate smoke there.
firing all the cannons.
John?
Now you're talking to me.
You're out of your  mind.
Yeah.
It's a special breed.
this boat.
It was born with a bulbous bow.
A very big bulbous bow
it was born with.
An oosik is a bone
that's inside of a walrus.
Walrus has the largest penis
for any animal.
Her bulbous bow.
And I'll put a few pots
in a little pile for 'em.
Don't ever turn your back
on a walrus.
on a damn Time Bandit either.
Hang on.
I'm gonna turn here.
Roger.
I know you're trying to be
a funny guy. but there is
a string right in front
of you. man.
Don't worry.
I can see it.
Oh. boy.
He's heading
right for our gear.
- Yeah. Roger!
-Roger!
Wow. wow. wow!
He's not stopping.
Yeah!
Come on. bring it in.
Bring it in!
Looking good on this side.
Yeah!
We got it.
That's one.
Keep it coming.
I don't think he's pulling
my gear.
He's just barreling
down the string.
Coming in. baby.
Coming in hot.
Looking good!
Port in a little bit.
Coming around quick!
Whoo-hoo!
We got it!
-We got her!
-Just the last one here.
He's got it!
Yeah!
We'll just give 'em back to
Sig just like that. guys.
That's all my gear right there.
Whole string is right there.
He's mowed right through.
That's gonna take all day
to get that untangled.
-All day.
-Yeah. you serious?
Go get 'em. Johnny.
I'm on my way right now
with a load of gear.
I'm gonna set over by you.
-We got this guy.
- Come on over here.
Going over.
Roadrunner out.
Beep. beep.
62 miles southwest...
We're coming up on
the farthest north string.
...on the Aleutian Lady.
This trip started off
with a bang.
We found crab. and now
I have to keep tracking.
I gotta stay on top of them.
Let's go. baby!
And I'm hoping my attempts
to follow 'em
are gonna pay off.
Oh. no way.
I'm so happy.
Come on crab!
Riders!
Oh. riders.
Two riders.
-Oh. yeah.
Damn.
Hell yeah. baby!
What I'm thinking is.
maybe we can bring
the Cornelia Marie out and just
transfer me at sea.
All right. sounds good.
Goodbye.
I'm about to go on the
Cornelia Marie as the captain.
Yee-haw!
This is fantastic.
Whoo!
I've gotta go tell Rick now
and see if he'll drop me in
the water. let Cornelia pick me
up. and then he can
keep on cruising.
-Whoo-hoo!
-Yeah!
Cornelia Marie.
Holy !
Time Bandit. baby!
110 miles northeast
of St. George Island.
Sig  gone.
He was running for the hills.
Chased off the Northwestern
right there.
Come on. baby!
First pot!
Whoo!
I know Sig was going northeast.
We're gonna corral these
crab and slam dunk this thing.
Come on. baby.
give us some love down there!
Come on. baby!
Coming up.
What have we got?
Come on. crabs.
Coming up.
Come on.
I need to see legs.
Come on. baby.
-Oh!
-Not much.
Aye. aye. aye.
Roger.
-You're good.
-Oh. no!
No.
Tango Uniform.
Tits up.
Dead. lame.
on arrival.
Come on. baby.
-Damn it.
-Nothing.
Uh...
This is not what we
were looking for.
Yeah. this is the same thing
over here. my friend.
-All right. stack it.
-Roger.
Crap.
Sig was going northeast.
Aye. aye. aye.
I'm kind of mad right now.
I'll be honest. because...
we spent hours and hours
untangling. you know.
all those pots
that Jonathan managed to. uh.
mess up for us.
So we gotta move fast.
We're approaching our string
that we set to the north.
And we'll see if it worked.
Come on. baby.
Come to papa.
Moment of truth.
We need a sign of life
in this one.
-What do we got?
-Whoa!
-Yeah!
There it is.
Yeah. baby!
-Nice.
- Let's go.
-That's what we want.
-Oh. yeah.
There's a lot
of real estate out here.
When you're tracking these
crabs. you know. you wanna
know how far it spreads
and where the cutoff is.
The problem is we don't have
enough pots here
to do what I wanna do.
On board.
I just need more gear.
Yeah. buddy.
The only guys that are around
me is Keith and John.
Tweedledee and Tweedledum off
to the east of me.
What is this?
-Man!
-Womp. womp. womp.
You know what. John?
How banged up are
you over there?
So how's it going over
there. gentlemen?
I'm just curious how operation
Wizard-Bandit's working out
for you two.
-Ah. .
What is this?
Hansen. what do you want?
Hansen.
I wish you could block callers
on the VHF.
Well. I think you aren't
seeing anything.
-No good.
-Damn it.
What the ?
We're gonna need something
better than this.
- Sucks.
Four.
-Tell me I'm wrong.
-We ain't got no crab.
-What do you want. Sigurd?
-Hell yeah!
-Look at that. baby!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
I wasn't blindly tracking
these crab to the northeast.
-Yeah. baby!
-Yeah!
Now. if you want to get
back on the crab.
you're gonna do
exactly what I say.
That sounded -- that's not nice.
Damn it!
Aye. aye. aye. aye. aye.
This is not good.
I mean. we gotta find
the edge of the school.
But I don't have enough gear
to do what I wanna do.
I want a season out of this
school. not just a pick.
Yeah. dude.
What the hell?
This is a nightmare.
But at the same time...
there's too much at stake.
I might regret this one.
Yeah. what are you
thinking there?
I need one of you to come
on the east side of me.
one on the west side.
What I'm seeing here.
I think they're west. so...
How about I take west
and you take east?
Keith. sound good?
John. you go west...
- OK.
-...I'm going east.
But we know
how you fish things.
So no lies.
no BS.
-It doesn't end.
No cloak and dagger.
Try to pull anything.
it's gonna --
Keith. oh. just please die
before me.
Yeah!
These are good numbers.
To stay on this school.
I mean. I'd work
with the devil himself.
Or two devils if I have to.
Colburnabub.
Beelzeburn.
When you work with a Hansen.
you work with a weasel.
-Damn it!
-But I don't have a choice.
I mean.
it's a gamble.
Well. we'll see what happens.
60 miles southwest...
aboard the Aleutian Lady.
Yep. roger here.
Right on. buddy.
Jake. come on up here. man.
Look. right over there. man.
Yeah. I'm pretty excited.
I'm not excited. though.
about transferring
from here to there.
Here we go.
All right. you guys
ready out there?
Hey. get a long...
I do not like not
having the control.
I'll get a little
closer over there. Cody.
They are getting damn close.
Come on. Cody.
Got it?
Here we go.
We're pulling the line across.
It's like going fishing.
except for right now
I'm the bait.
OK. let's get him hooked up
in the hook.
Go for Jacob's ladder.
-There he goes.
Here you go!
Pull. pull. pull.
Good luck. Jake!
Yee-haw!
Let's give him
a welcome. boys.
-What's up. baby?
-What's up. captain?
-You ready?
-We're ready!
Let's go.
One Jake Anderson is aboard.
- I made it.
-What's up. Jake?
-You made it.
-Yeah.
-Welcome aboard. dude.
-You made magic happen.
-Yeah.
-It's good to be here.
Yeah. good to see you. dude.
Welcome aboard.
Helm's yours.
This thing is
a Lamborghini. man.
I can't believe I'm sitting
in Phil's chair.
Could be the beginning
of something really good.
Yes. you did.
I wanted you to take
the initiative to do it.
and you did.
-OK.
You know. you might be
doing this without me.
You should be able to shine.
See just how good you are.
64 miles northeast.
Well. here they come.
It was never my plan to work
with these guys. but I mean.
beggars can't be
choosers. right?
But the bottom line is.
we're just looking for the edge
of that crab.
All right.
I'm moving in. guys.
One guy on the east.
one on the west.
Keith. you gonna take
the east side?
Roger.
I can't believe
I'm working with Sig.
The Roadrunner.
and the Coyote working
with the Tasmanian Devil.
The three amigos.
One of 'em will probably have
some blank pots.
But that's how we're gonna find
the edge of this crab.
The bow looks good. Keith.
She's looking good.
Like a rust bucket.
I've always told you that
Time Bandit's the best looking
boat out here.
Keith's boat looks
like a catfish.
Northwestern's pretty.
like a woman.
Hey. Sig. I'll start a half
a mile from you.
and they'll move out
to a mile.
OK. let's fire them off
in three.
Set.
In three. two --
One.
Let her go. guys.
Let her go.
-OK.
-Going over!
OK. we're gonna set same
time. so get them over the side.
OK. bombs away. guys.
Send our paratroopers down.
We're hitting the enemy hard
here. all three of us.
As Winston Churchill
once said.
"We're gonna fight 'em on
the land. we're gonna fight
'em at sea. we're gonna fight
'em in the air."
We're gonna fight 'em
on the sea floor.
But I like Winston Churchill.
sort of.
Maybe I don't.
I don't know him.
I never met him.
Dump it.
Now let's see if there's any
luck in you guys.
I just wanna tell you.
"Good luck."
We're looking
for these purebloods.
these larger northern king crab.
If we all hit.
it's a win-win.
Just don't let 'em get away.
Looking for the edge
of the school.
I can't believe I'm working
with this guy.
I can only hope
this isn't a waste of time.
...right now. guys.
Come on. baby.
Big pots. big pots. big pots.
Yeah!
Whoo!
Oh. yes!
-Hi-ya!
-Whoo-hoo-hoo!
-Big baby.
-Monsters!
That's what we're looking
for right there.
-Whoo!
- Crab city. baby.
Look at this big northern crab.
right there.
We are in the middle
of the city.
Big boys!
Roadrunner is in the crab.
Beep. beep. beep. beep.
beep. beep. beep.
Let's go!
Come on. come on. come on.
What do we got?
Ah.
What is this?
That one's way back there.
I mean. we're just trying to
find the edge of that crab.
so be patient.
Colburns are not known
for their patience.
I knew I was getting
the short end of the stick.
Every time you hear
my voice. you relax.
You're going to a deeper
and deeper relaxation.
Every pot that hits the deck.
you're going to a deeper.
deeper relaxation.
-Oh. yeah. baby!
-Here it comes!
We're in 'em.
-Here we go!
That's a nice looking king crab
right there.
All right. guys.
The edge starts right at 25.4.
Nice!
Perfect.
Mark it down. man.
Oh. yeah. baby.
Got him. guys!
We're killing it here!
Whoo-hoo!
Nice job. guys.
Good work.
Riders.
-Whoo.
-Riders.
-Let's go. crab!
-Yeah!
Unce. unce. unce.
Load 'em up. boys.
Load 'em up.
You and you and you.
I love you guys.
On the meat.
And you have the highest price
we've ever seen in our lives.
Whoo!
In one hour. you can catch
$100.000 worth of crab.
I got this for you. Mama.
It's all good.
And then be in a position
to leapfrog each other.
-That's the end game.
-Take no prisoners.
yeah!
What about them big pots?
When you do come together
and you can find crab
like this. it's the big picture
that matters.
I love it!
Oh-ho-ho-ho!
But the North is a very
dangerous place to fish.
and it's just gonna get worse.
Watch your rail.
-Back off.
-Damn!
Go. go. go. go!
-Typhoon. how long?
-It's 1.500 miles wide.
Oh!
We're gonna get
our asses kicked.
Fire!
Fire. there's a fire
in the back!
Watch out guys.
-Man down!
He's got knocked out.
We have a new member
to the family.
OK. you wanna give
this a try?
Everything changes in winter.
Whoa!
man!
The weather is in control.
We're taking on water.
Everyone thinks they know...
what they're in for.
They don't.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm